[I won't work overtime today]
[本宫今天不加班]
[Episode 9]
[第九集]
Dear concubines
各位爱妃
Please take your seats
都请入座吧
Yuer
玉儿
Emperor
皇上
The concubine embroidered a brocade with her own hands
臣妾亲手绣了幅锦缎
Want to dedicate to the emperor
想要献给皇上
Emperor
皇上
This is the brocade sent by Concubine Zhao
这是赵嫔妃送上的锦缎
Nice
不错
Emperor
皇上
Every stitch and thread on this
这上面一针一线
It was all sewn by my concubine herself
都是臣妾自己缝的
Concubine
臣妾
In that remote cold palace
在那偏僻的冷宫之中
All right
行了
Go back and sit down
回去坐着吧
There is still a lot of resentment between words
言语之间还诸多怨气
It's really stupid
实在是蠢笨
Emperor
皇上
Concubine is not like Zhao Concubine's sister
嫔妾不似赵嫔妹妹
So ingenious
这般心灵手巧
Just prepared a dance
只是准备了一支舞
I also hope the emperor
还望皇上
Don't dislike your concubines
莫要嫌弃嫔妾呀
Let me see
让朕瞧瞧
The string breaks
琴弦崩断
Always bodes on the wall
向来是不祥之兆
Concubine Jing not only made a fool of herself this time
静嫔这下不仅出了丑
I'm afraid it will be
恐怕还会因此
Make the emperor disgusted
让皇上厌恶呐
Your Majesty
皇 皇上
Okay, go back and rest
好了 回去歇着吧
I wish the emperor a long life
臣妾祝皇上 万寿无疆
It was also specially prepared for the emperor
也特意为皇上准备了
A little thought from my concubine
臣妾的一点心意
Compared to
相比起来
Just now, Concubine Zhao herself
刚刚赵嫔自己
Embroidered silk and satin
绣的绸缎
It's a joke
就是个笑话
Wei Guifei is not only
魏贵妃 不仅仅
I'm here to offer treasure to the emperor
是来给皇上献宝的
Also here to demonstrate to us
也是来向我们示威的
I wonder if the emperor likes it
不知皇上是否喜欢
Not bad, I like it very much
不错 朕很是喜欢
In the heart of my concubine
在臣妾心中
Your Majesty is the sky full of stars
陛下就是那满天星辰
Will be eclipsed
都将黯然失色的
The only sun
唯一太阳
This is also the meaning of this dragon robe
这也是这件龙袍的寓意
Wei Guifei has a heart
魏贵妃有心了
I think this dragon robe
我看这龙袍
There is still a phoenix robe to match
还差一件凤袍相搭配
Xiao Xu Zi
小许子
Rushing for Wei Guifei overnight
连夜为魏贵妃赶制
Thank you, Your Majesty
谢皇上
Emperor
皇上
He Concubine's sister's birthday gift
何嫔妹妹的寿礼
It hasn't been presented yet
还没呈上来呢
They sent these
他们发的这些
Why didn't you make any progress at all
怎么一点长进都没有
Gratitude for meeting
感恩遇见
Accompany you like a shadow
如影随形陪伴你
A big man
一个大男人
Send me pictures like this
给我发这种照片
The meat is not disgusting
肉不肉麻呀
It's too disgusting, isn't it
也太恶心了吧
If you are well, it will be sunny
你若安好 便是晴天
May you pass through thousands of sails
愿您千帆过尽
Return is still a teenager
归来仍是少年
Am I not a teenager now
我现在不是少年吗
It's just that this group photo is released
只是这合照放出来
With his consent
经过他同意了吗
Actually put this kind of
竟然把这种
Black historical photos are sent out
黑历史照片发出来
Am I
我是不是
Being too lenient with you
对你过于宽容了
This is quite innovative
这倒是挺有新意的啊
[-♪ Say goodbye to all your worries ♪]
[-♪跟所有的烦恼说拜拜♪] -感恩的心
[♪ Say hihi to all the happiness ♪]
[♪跟所有的快乐说hihi♪]
[-♪ Happy birthday, dear, dear ♪]
[-♪亲爱的亲爱的生日快乐♪] -这
The brain is not working well
脑子不好使
What are these monsters and monsters
这都是些什么妖魔鬼怪
Don't study the business carefully when you have time
有时间不好好钻研业务
Get me these here
在这儿给我搞这些
Looks like the boss's birthday
看来这老板过生日
How to flatter is also a matter of science
怎么拍马屁也是门学问
Why didn't she give it to me
她怎么还不给我
Day blessings
发生日祝福啊
Why didn't you see Concubine He's gift
怎不见何妃的礼物
Reply to the emperor's words
回皇上的话
Although my concubines are not as good as
臣妾虽不如
Sister Jingbin is like that
静嫔姐姐那样
Be good at singing and dancing
能歌善舞
But also ready
但也准备了
A little thought
一点小小的心思
That's it
就这
Are you fooling the emperor
你在糊弄皇上吗
Let's get started
开始吧
Common in famine years
遇荒年 每常见
All the floods this year have been flooded
就中今年 洪水皆淹偏
Parents are separated without love
父母分离无可恋
Fortunately, I hope that the king will save the strong family man
幸望君王 救取壮家汉
A bed of spring leek green
一畦春韭绿
The fragrance of ten miles of rice flowers
十里稻花香
There is no hunger and discouragement in prosperous times
盛世无饥馁
Why do you need to be busy with farming and weaving
何须耕织忙
What does this mean
这是何意啊
Reply to the emperor's words
回皇上的话
The Yellow River is flooding this summer
今夏黄河泛滥成灾
Displacement of the population
百姓流离失所
These two children
这两个孩子
Exactly what I get in the folk
正是我在民间所得
Under the rule of the emperor
在皇上的治理之下
People's lives have been calmed down
百姓的生活得以平复
What they're trying to say
他们想说的
It is the thousands of victims of the disaster in Qian Qian
正是千千万万灾民
What I want to say to you
想对您说的话
Good very good
好 甚好
Compared with me enjoying all the delicacies in the world
相比起朕 尽享天下珍馐
Glory and wealth
荣华富贵
I hope to have fun with the people
朕更希望与民同乐
Xiao Xu Zi
小许子
Emperor
皇上
Reward
赏
[Now we just have to wait]
[现在只需要等待了]
[Remember the first time we met]
[还记得第一次见面]
[I accidentally hurt you because of my carelessness]
[因我的大意误伤了您]
[You treat each other tolerantly regardless of past grudges]
[您不计前嫌 宽容相待]
[Every time you leave work]
[每次下班]
[You are the last]
[您都是最后一个]
[Leaving the company]
[离开公司]
[But still don't forget to care]
[却仍不忘关心]
[Our Work]
[我们的工作]
You're working overtime here alone
你 一个人在这里加班
[You wait a minute]
[你再等一下]
Have a good weekend and good night
周末愉快 晚安
[Be gentle with others and smile not stingy]
[温和待人 不吝啬笑容]
Good night Mr. Li
晚安 李总
What are you posting here
你这贴的是什么呀
[You told me]
[是您告诉了我]
[Just take it seriously]
[只要认认真真]
[Do what's in front of you]
[做好眼前的事]
[Even if it's insignificant]
[即使再微不足道]
[Just work hard]
[只要努力]
[Also worthy of being seen]
[也值得被看到]
[So gentle and excellent you]
[如此温柔优秀的您]
[Be sure to remember]
[一定要记住]
[No matter how busy you are at work]
[无论工作多忙]
[Also eat on time]
[也要按时吃饭]
[Only you are healthy]
[唯有您健健康康]
[To lead us]
[才能带领我们]
[Go on for a long time]
[长久地走下去]
Listen up, friends
各位朋友听好了
How to write a leader's birthday copy
领导生日文案怎么写
Just remember three elements
只要记住三个要素
First unique
第一 独特
Second sincerity
第二 真挚
Third, do whatever you like
第三 投其所好
First, from a unique angle
首先 以独特的角度
And those cookie-cutter copywriters
和那些千篇一律的文案
Expand the distinction
展开区别
Second sincerity
第二 真挚
In a slightly literary tone
用略显文艺的语气
Make sensational sensation
进行煽情
Inject true feelings into words
给文字注入真情实感
Then do whatever you like
接着 投其所好
As a
作为一个
Big narcissistic pig's trotters
自恋的大猪蹄子
See others' respect for him
看到别人对他的敬意
He will surely be rejoiced in his heart
他一定会心生欢喜
Triumphant
得意洋洋
In the end
最后
Show concern for his body
对他的身体表达关怀
Not only embodies
不仅体现了
We have a close relationship
我们之间的关系密切
He also secretly expressed his loyalty
还暗戳戳地表达了忠心
Perfect precision strike
完美实现精准打击
Have you learned it
你 学会了吗
You woke up
你睡醒了
[You're awake]
[你睡醒了]
What do you mean
什么意思
Hello Du Xiaosong
喂 杜小松
Who the hell sent me back yesterday
昨天到底谁送我回来的
[It seems to say]
[好像说]
[It was Mr. Li who carried you home]
[是李总抱着你回家的]
What
什么
Impossible
不可能
Impossible impossible
不可能 不可能
There's no way I can do such a thing
我不可能做这种事情
Especially for Li Su
尤其是对李溯
How could I possibly
我怎么可能呢
He Mingyue
何明月
If you dare to drink again, I will
你要是再敢喝酒 我就
He Jiaojiao, right
何皎皎是吧
Accelerated negotiations
谈判速度加快
Within three months
三个月内
I want everything
我要所有事情
All on the right track
都步入正轨
Sister Jiaojiao, please listen to my explanation
皎皎姐 你听我解释嘛
You weren't yesterday
你们昨天不是
Nothing happened
什么事都没发生
If anything really happened
要真发生了什么
Do you think you can still
你觉得你还能
Stand here alive and talk to me
活着站在这跟我说话吗
Release
松开
You loosen, too
你也松开
What happened to you yesterday
你怎么了 昨天
I drank too much yesterday
昨天我喝多了
I'm sorry, Mr. Li
对不起 李总
I swear
我发誓
I'm never drinking again
我再也不喝酒了
You really shouldn't drink anymore
你确实不应该再喝酒了
So what happened yesterday
所以昨天的事情
Please also consider it
还请您当作
Nothing ever happened
什么也没有发生过
Nothing happened
什么都没发生
Do you know what you did yesterday
你知道你昨天干嘛了吗
Whatever I did yesterday
不管我昨天干了什么
Please don't take it seriously
都请您别当真
Just having fun
只是玩玩而已
You play the same way with others
你和别人也这么玩
It really opened my eyes
真是让我大开眼界啊
I didn't expect you to play so freely
没想到你玩这么开
No matter who I play with
不管我和谁玩
Don't bother you, Mr. Li
不劳李总您费心了
You
你
He Jiaojiao
何皎胶
I'm sorry, Mr. Li
对不起 李总
All I'm focused on is work right now
我现在一心只有工作
I'm going back to work
我要回去工作了
You
你
Don't you work
你不工作吗
Waiting to go to Africa
等着去非洲啊
Sister Jiaojiao, you didn't last night
皎皎姐 你昨晚不会
What are you thinking about
你瞎想什么呢
I'm not thinking about anything
我没瞎想什么
What are you thinking
是你瞎想什么呀
Duty cycle
工作周期
Compressed to three months
压缩到三个月了
Get back to work
快回去工作
Mr. Li doesn't seem to be anything
李总好像也不是什么
Someone who takes advantage of the situation
乘虚而入的人呀
Why just looked like
怎么刚刚看起来
It's like he's been taken advantage of
好像他被占了便宜
Morning Mr. Li
早 李总
Your milk
您的牛奶
President
总裁大人
Where are you going
你要去哪
He Jiaojiao
何皎皎
You, you, what are you doing
你 你 你在干吗
President, I'm fine
总裁大人 我好好的
I want to drink water
我想喝水
He Jiaojiao, let me tell you
何皎皎 我跟你讲
You're playing with fire
你在玩火啊
Come quickly
快点 来嘛
Drink water
喝水
Thank you
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Hurry up.
谢谢 快点 谢谢
Give
给
No, no, no, no
不不不
I want you to feed me
我要你喂我
I want you to feed me with your mouth
我要你用嘴喂我
There are assassins
有刺客
I knew it
我就知道
You're a horny big pig's trotter
你是个好色的大猪蹄子
Today I'm gonna do justice for heaven
今天我就要替天行道
He Jiaojiao
何皎皎
Listen to her say that
听她这么说
She is
她就是
Is deliberately playing with my feelings
在故意玩弄我的感情
Mr. Li, what did you say
李总 您说什么
Don't ask if you shouldn't
不该问就别问
Take it down
拿下去
Mr. Li, this is a glass of milk before going to bed
李总 这睡前一杯牛奶
A glass of milk in the morning
早晨一杯牛奶
Isn't it your habit
不是您的习 习惯吗
I said you
我说你
Why are you talking so much now
现在话怎么这么多
Take it when I ask you to take it
让你拿走就拿走
Take it away
拿走 拿走
Don't waste it
别浪费了
No drinking
不准喝
Down
倒了
Additionally
另外
Five minutes later
五分钟之后
Hold executive meetings
召开高管会议
Recent work efficiency
最近工作效率
Why is it so slow
怎么这么慢
Okay, Mr. Li
好的 李总
I'll inform you right away
我马上去通知
Komatsu
小松
Help Sister Li finish it
你帮李姐完成一下
Finishing touches
最后的收尾工作
Our recruitment activity this time
咱们这次的招聘活动
Even if it's over
就算结束了
I didn't think we could actually finish it
没想到我们真的能完成
Sister Jiaojiao
皎皎姐
I'm not flattering
我不是拍马屁啊
You take care of the work
你处理起工作来
Not like a newbie at all
一点都不像个新手
After all, it has been hosted several times
毕竟是主持过几次
Show girl selection person
秀女选拔的人
Can it be the same
能一样吗
My Mr. Wei, you're back
我的魏总 你可回来了
Mr. Wei, we all miss you so much
魏总 我们都可想你了
Why do you look so like Concubine Wei
怎么那么像魏贵妃
You showed up after all
你终究还是出现了
I've been waiting for you for a long time
等你很久了